<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">MobileBankingCompose</string>

    <string name="russian">Русский</string>
    <string name="uzbek">O\'zbekcha</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="lastName">Last Name</string>
    <string name="firstName">First Name</string>
    <string name="phoneNumber">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="send_again">Send again</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>

    <string name="text_verification_sent_number">Code sent to\n%1$s</string>
    <string name="text_verification_timer">Code send in\n%1$s</string>
    <string name="registration">Registration</string>
    <string name="enter_pin_code">Enter Pin Code</string>
    <string name="enter_new_pin_code">Enter Pin Code</string>

    <string name="text_policy_title">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="text_accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="text_policy_agreement">I agree to all terms.</string>
    <string name="text_policy_subtitle">Service privacy policy</string>
    <string name="text_policy_details">1. Introduction. This Privacy Policy describes the types of
        "Personal Information" (information that is identifiable to a particular person) that is
        collected (directly or through service providers) in connection with the mobile downloadable
        application ("App") and related services (collectively, the "Service") offered by your
        financial institution ("we" or "us"). This Privacy Policy is intended to supplement the
        disclosures in any Privacy Policy that you may have already been presented by us in
        connection with online banking or other services.
        \n\n2.
        Eligibility. The Service is offered only to individual residents of the United States,
        excluding its territories, who can form legally binding contracts under applicable law.
        Without limiting the foregoing, the Service is not offered to minors. Other restrictions
        and eligibility requirements for the Service apply as described in the mobile application
        Terms of Use. We do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from or about individuals
        under 18 years of age. Please do not submit such information to us, and as a parent or
        legal guardian, please do not allow your children to submit Personal Information without
        your permission. By using the App or the Service, you represent that you meet these
        requirements and that you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
        \n\n3.
        What Types of Personal Information We May Collect. We may collect Personal Information
        about you, which may include: name, postal address, zip code, e-mail address, telephone
        number, account numbers, payment card expiration date, payment card identification or
        verification numbers, social security number, mobile device location, and other information
        that we can use to contact you, verify your identity, provide the functionality available
        through use of the App and the Service, and manage risks, such as information maintained
        about you by identity verification services and consumer reporting agencies, including
        credit bureaus, and payment and other transaction information, and history for payments
        and other transactions in which you participate through the Service, and any Personal
        Information that you may enter into information blocks present in the App interface or
        made available through the Service.\n\n4.
        How We May Collect Personal Information About You. We may collect Personal Information
        about you from the following sources:\n\na.
        a. We may collect information regarding your mobile device such as device settings, unique
        device identifiers, information about your location, and analytical information that may
        assist with diagnostics and performance. For your convenience, you may be asked to grant
        permission for access to your mobile devices geolocation data. This information may be
        collected when you use certain services that are dependent on your mobile devices location
        (such as the location of an ATM or in store transactions).  Information that you input to
        the App or that the App collects automatically;\n\nb. Your use of the App and the Service,
        and your interactions with customer care, including information you enter or speak,
        and information transmitted by your computer or mobile device or other devices you use
        as part of your receipt of the Service;\n\nc.
        We may also collect Personal Information about you from others, such as Affiliates, or other
        companies (such as for fraud detection).\n\n5.
        How We May Share Personal Information About You. We share Personal Information about you
        only as permitted by law.
    </string>
    <string name="prompt_info_use_app_password">FingerPrint Pasword</string>
    <string name="enter">Enter</string>
    <string name="phone_not_found">Phone not found</string>
    <string name="password_not_found">wrong password</string>
    <string name="forget_password">Forgot password!</string>
    <string name="phone_content">To get a verification code, first confirm the recovery phone number</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="signIn">Sign In</string>
    <string name="change_password">Change Password</string>
    <string name="new_password">New password</string>
    <string name="confirm_passord">Confirm password</string>
    <string name="password_not_equals">Passwors not equals</string>
    <string name="erroMessage">Something  is wrong please try again</string>
    <string name="token_is_wrong">Please try again</string>
    <string name="text_skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="text_ready">Ready</string>
    <string name="text_pin_code_enter">Enter Pin Code</string>
    <string name="error_pi_code">Wrong Code</string>

    <string name="prompt_info_title">Title</string>
    <string name="prompt_info_subtitle">Subtitle</string>
    <string name="prompt_info_description">Description</string>
    <string name="text_resend">Send again</string>
    <string name="text_verification_error">Please try again!</string>
    <string name="have_account">I have already account!</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="enter_phone_number">Enter phone number</string>
    <string name="buttonText">Continue</string>
    <string name="enter_phone_code">Enter code</string>
    <string name="approve">Approve</string>
    <string name="enter_code">Enter the code which we send you to the number\n%1$s</string>
    <string name="send_again_in">Send again\n%1$s</string>
    <string name="registraration_a">Registration</string>
    <string name="create_password">Create password</string>
    <string name="confirm_password_a">Confirm the password</string>

    //pasword required
    <string name="create_required">Create as required</string>
    <string name="required_one">At least 8 or not more than 20 (required)</string>
    <string name="required_two">At least one letter (required)</string>
    <string name="required_three">At least one number (required)</string>
    <string name="required_four">Typing cyr. characters prohibited (required)</string>
    <string name="required_five">At least one capital letter</string>
    <string name="required_six">At least one specific symbol</string>
    <string name="data_agreement">Data Processing Agreement</string>
    <string name="privacy_agreement">I fully agree with the terms of the User Agreement</string>
    <string name="pin">PIN</string>
    <string name="create_pin">Create a PIN</string>
    <string name="repeat_pin">Repeat the PIN</string>
    <string name="wrong_code">Code is not match</string>
    <string name="transfer_card">Transfer to Card</string>
    <string name="transfer_wallet">Transfer to Wallet</string>
    <string name="transfer_account">Transfer to Account</string>
    <string name="transfer_requisites">Tranfer to requisites</string>
    <string name="transfer_fundraising">Fundraising</string>
    <string name="transfer_rocket">Rocket</string>
    <string name="transfer">Transfer</string>
</resources>